adgitize.com 2011-03-06

# Adgitize Privacy Policy

Adgitize respects and protects your privacy when you are using our Adgitize website. Information that may specifically identify you as an individual is never shared with third parties. 

**Adgitize and Cookies**

Upon your first visit to Adgitize, Adgitize may send a "cookie" to your computer. Cookies are used by many sites, an internet search on 'cookies' will provide you with the information you need. The intent of cookies is to identify your computer preferences and searching patterns. Adgitize will not disclose its cookies to third parties except as required by a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order. Most internet browsers are set up to accept cookies. Although it is possible to reset your computer settings to inform you of cookies or to reject cookies, such actions may interfere with your use of Adgitize web site and services. 

**What Information Do We Collect?**

Adgitize does not secretly collect information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information during the registration process. This information is used to contact you for payment, notifications and potential changes. Adgitize notes and saves information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address with each query. This information is used to verify our records and to provide more relevant services to users.

**Links to Other Sites**

The sites displayed as ad results or linked to by Adgitize are developed by people over whom Adgitize has no control. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. It is important that you preview their Privacy Policy and remove any cookies from your computer if you have any concerns. 

**Adgitize Shared Information**

Adgitize may share information about you with advertisers, sponsors, and other third parties. This shared information is in the form of compiled data that does not identify individuals. For example, we may disclose keyword searches, or the amount of time spent in searching at Adgitize. Please be aware, however, that we will release specific personal information about you if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order. 

**Your consent and changes to the Privacy Policy**

By using Adgitize and our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as outlined in this policy and to our Terms of Service Policy. Adgitize may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any such changes will be dated and posted on this page. The purpose of this Policy is to make you an informed Internet user - fully aware of what information is collected and the uses for compiled information. 

**Additional questions?**

If you still have questions feel free to **contact us.**

* * *
